var QuestionList = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "How to write hello world in CPP?",
        options: ["cout<<\"Hello world\"",
            "printf(\"Hello world\")",
            "print \"Hello World\""],
        answer: [1]
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "How to write hello world in Python?",
        options: ["cout<<\"Hello world\"",
            "printf(\"Hello world\")",
            "print \"Hello World\""],
        answer: [3]
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "How to write hello world in Java?",
        options: ["System.print(\"Hello world\")",
            "System.out.println(\"Hello world\")",
            "print \"Hello World\""],
        answer: [1, 2]
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "How to write hello world in Java Script?",
        options: ["console.log('Hello World')",
            "System.out.println(\"Hello world\")",
            "print \"Hello World\""],
        answer: [1]
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Does java supports Interfaces?",
        options: ["Yes",
            "No",
            "Depends on operating system"],
        answer: [1]
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What is the type of : 2.34 in javascript?",
        options: ["Float",
            "Number",
            "Double"],
        answer: [2]
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "How to create object in JavaScript?",
        options: ["let obj = new ClassName();",
            "let obj = {}",
            "let obj = new Object()"],
        answer: [1, 2, 3]
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which is the optimum searching algorithm?",
        options: ["Linear Search",
            "Fast Search",
            "Binary Search"],
        answer: [3]
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Is java same as Javascript?",
        options: ["Yes, they are same",
            "False",
            "Same in Linux"],
        answer: [2]
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which sorting algorithm given n logn time complexity?",
        options: ["Merge Sort",
            "Heap Sort",
            "Bubble Sort"],
        answer: [1, 2]
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "What is the command to create a new folder/ directory?",
        options: ["mkdir",
            "createDirectory",
            "makeFolder"],
        answer: [1]
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "What will be the output of following in JS: <code>2===\"2\"</code>",
        options: ["True",
            "False",
            "Browser dependent"],
        answer: [2]
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "Which of the following are Object in javascript?",
        options: ["Array",
            "Function",
            "The one declared using new keyword"],
        answer: [1, 2, 3]
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "How to comment code in Javascript?",
        options: ["using //",
            "using /* */",
            "using <!-  ->"],
        answer: [1, 2]
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "What is typescript?",
        options: ["It is script tag with type attribute",
            "Superset of javascript, with defined types",
            "Same as javascript"],
        answer: [2]
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "How to declare an integer value in typescript?",
        options: ["int x;",
            "Integer x;",
            "let x: number"],
        answer: [3]
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "How to compile typescript?",
        options: ["tsc filename",
            "tsc -w filname",
            "tsc -w"],
        answer: [1, 2, 3]
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "What is the type of &lt;button> tag in typescript?",
        options: ["Button",
            "HTMLElement",
            "ButtonTag"],
        answer: [2]
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "How to decalre function with integer return type in TypeScript?",
        options: ["function sum():number{}",
            "function number:sum(){}",
            "int sum(){}"],
        answer: [1, 2]
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: "How to pass number as parameter in TypeScript functions?",
        options: ["function sum(x:number, y:number){}",
            "int sum(int x, int y){}",
            "function sum(int x, int y){}"],
        answer: [1]
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: "What is the extension of TypeScript file?",
        options: [".tc",
            ".tsx",
            ".ts"],
        answer: [3]
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: "How to declare Integer Array in TypeScript?",
        options: ["let arr = Array(int);",
            "let arr:number[];",
            "let arr:Array<number>"],
        answer: [2, 3]
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        question: "Which of the following are benefits of TypeScript?",
        options: ["Reduces bugs in production",
            "Makes things complex without reason",
            "Helps in ensuring type safety"],
        answer: [1, 3]
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        question: "What is the full form of ES6?",
        options: ["Ecma Script 6",
            "Engineer Script 6",
            "Elegant Script 6"],
        answer: [1]
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        question: "TypeScript was developed by?",
        options: ["Google",
            "Microsoft",
            "Facebok"],
        answer: [2]
    }
];
